I was watching the video that you posted
estaba viendo el el video que publicaste
So it's directed at me You're
Entonces está dirigiendo a mí me estás
mentioning that Where I
mencionando eso donde yo de donde yo
come from it's something totally offensive I mean
vengo es algo totalmente ofensivo o sea
if I saw you I would probably punch you in
si yo te viera probablemente te partiría
the face yeah or what But because we're
la cara sí o qué Pero porque estamos
talking about another culture
hablando de otra cultura
Why have I mentioned you Yes because you
porque te he mencionado Sí porque me
're telling me first that you don't know
estás diciendo primero que no sabes
who I am I don't know what I do
quién soy yo no sabes a qué me dedico
You've never been to Medellín yeah do
vos nunca has venido a Medellín sí
n't come because you'd be the typical
no vengas porque serías el típico
foreigner who's supposed to be
extranjero que
and this is supposed to
le dan y se supone que esto me tiene que
scare me It's that you're like a
dar miedo Es que eres como un mono
literal monkey I mean it's exaggerated You come and
literal o sea es exagerado vienes y me
tell me You laughed at me I punch your
dices tú te reíste de mí yo partir tu
face We're not in a game we're in
cara no estamos en un juego estamos en
the jungle bro how the [ __ ] did you go from
la jungla el bro como pasaste de
being the Viking of the community to playing
ser el vikingo de la comunidad hacer la
Dallas
perrita de Dallas